没有你 圣诞节我会过得很忧郁
I'll have a blue christmas without you
光是想着你我都很忧郁
I'll be so blue just thinking about you
绿色的圣诞树上挂着红色的装饰
Decorations of red on a green christmas tree
和以前不同 因为亲爱的你不在
Won't be the same dear, if you're not here with me
而当蓝色雪花开始坠落的时候
And when those blue snowflakes start falling
我就回想起那些忧郁的记忆
Thats when those blue memories start calling
你会过的很好的白色圣诞
You'll be doing all right, with your christmas of white
但我将过一个忧郁的蓝色圣诞
But I'll have a blue, blue blue blue christmas
没有你 圣诞节我会过得很忧郁
I'll have a blue christmas without you
光是想着你我都很忧郁
I'll be so blue just thinking about you
你会过的很好的白色圣诞
You'll be doing all right, with your christmas of white
但我将过一个忧郁的蓝色圣诞
But I'll have a blue, blue blue blue christmas
你会过的很好的白色圣诞
You'll be doing all right, with your christmas of white
但我将过一个忧郁的蓝色圣诞
But I'll have a blue, blue blue blue christmas